{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "yo", "answer": "soy" },
    { "prompt": "tú", "answer": "eres" },
    { "prompt": "él", "answer": "es" },
    { "prompt": "ella", "answer": "es" },
    { "prompt": "soy", "answer": "yo" },
    { "prompt": "eres", "answer": "tú" },
    { "prompt": "es", "answer": "él/ella" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "yo", "answer": "tengo" },
    { "prompt": "tú", "answer": "tienes" },
    { "prompt": "él", "answer": "tiene" },
    { "prompt": "ella", "answer": "tiene" },
    { "prompt": "tengo", "answer": "yo" },
    { "prompt": "tienes", "answer": "tú" },
    { "prompt": "tiene", "answer": "él/ella" }
  ]
}
